Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES VI. Regions, 1964-1980
Sophia Smith Collection
Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES VI. Regions
1964-80
Planned Parenthood Federation of America
371a_s6
12.5 linear feet
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
This series consists of the national office's records on the various regional offices of PPFA and includes the following types of materials: minutes, affiliation materials, correspondence, memos, reports, publicity, committee files, workshop files, project files, financial materials, and subject files. This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
This series consists of the national office's records on the various regional offices of PPFA and includes the following types of materials: minutes, affiliation materials, correspondence, memos, reports, publicity, committee files, workshop files, project files, financial materials, and subject files. Regional offices oversee affiliate activities and report to the national office. The regions are as follows: Mid-Atlantic; Great Lakes; Midwest; Southwest/ South-Central; Western; Southeast; and North Atlantic/Northeast.
NOTE: To view the series descriptions and contents lists, click on the series links below. Some files are quite large and may take several minutes to load, depending on your internet connection.
This collection is organized into ten series:
I. Chronological Files
II. Classified Files
Part 1
Part 2
III. Publications
IV. Subject Files
V. Affiliates
Part 1
Part 2
VI. Regions
VII. Minutes
VIII. Foreign
IX. Guttmacher
[X. Restricted]
PPFA has closed records created January 1, 1985 or later, with the exception of many published materials which are open to research. All records having to do with clinic defense and security are closed. PPFA has closed a small section of files in box 206 for fifty years. Researchers may request access to restricted materials from PPFA.
The Margaret Sanger Papers Microfilm Edition: Smith College Collection Series, edited by Esther Katz, et al., University Publications of America, 1995
Periodic additions to the collection are expected.
PPFA deposited these records in 1988. Various departments have since sent miscellaneous additions.
Best, Winfield; Guttmacher, Alan Frank, 1898-; McCormick, Katherine Dexter, 1876-1967; Rose, D. Kenneth; Sanger, Margaret, 1879-1966; Wattleton, Faye; Alan Guttmacher Institute--History; American Birth Control League--History; Abortion--Law and legislation-United States--History--Sources; Abortion services--History--Sources; Birth Control Clinical Research Bureau (New York, N.Y.)--History; Birth Control Federation of America--History; International Planned Parenthood Federation--History; Planned Parenthood Federation of America--History; Planned Parenthood-World Population (U.S.)--History; Birth control clinics--United States--History--Sources; Birth control--History--20th century--Sources; Birth control--Developing countries--History--20th century--Sources; Contraceptives--Research--History; Hygiene, Sexual--History--20th century; Human reproduction--Political aspects; Population policy--History--20th century; Reproductive health--Statistics; Sex instruction--History; Women--Health and hygiene--United States--20th century; Women's health services--United States--20th century
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
See also the PPFA I Records.
Related material can be found in the Margaret Sanger Papers, Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College, and at the Library of Congess.
- SERIES VI. REGIONS
  - Regional, General
    - Correspondence, Memos
      - 1980 (Box 186, Folder 1)
      - 1970-74 (Box 186, Folder 2)
      - 1975-79 (Box 186)
    - Estimated Minimum Need for Contraceptive Services by PP Regions 1971 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Regional Fund Raisers 1972-74 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Guidelines for a Reg. Resources Review Committee 1975 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - HEW Sterilization Regulations, Legal (Paul, Eve) 1979 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Job Description
      - Associate Director of Resources for Each Region 1972 (Box 186, Folder 7)
      - Regional Director 1976-79 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Monthly Reporting System 1972 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Policy Recommendations 1977 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - Medical Committees, Regional Medical Committees, Procedures 1972 (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - Public Affairs Network 1970-72 (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Regional Representatives, Discretionary Fund
      - 1970-73 (Box 186, Folder 13)
      - 1975-79 (Box 186)
    - Regional Representatives & Chairmen, Member Lists
      - 1969-72 (Box 186, Folder 14)
      - 1974-78 (Box 186)
    - Regional Organizations, Responsibilities of Representatives & Chairman & Director, Functions of Regional Councils
      - 1966-72 (Box 186, Folder 15)
      - 1980 (Box 186)
    - Regional Resources, Review Committee
      - Member Lists 1977 (Box 186, Folder 16)
      - Minutes 1979 (Box 186, Folder 17)
    - Regional Leadership Training Conference, Dallas 1965, 1968 (Box 186, Folder 18)
    - Regional Subcommittee, Report on PPWP Dues 1971 (Box 186, Folder 19)
    - Role of Regional Office Staff 1976 (Box 186, Folder 20)
    - Study of the Regions, (Jack Hood Vaughn) 1975 (Box 186, Folder 21)
    - Training Programs in the Regions 1972 (Box 186, Folder 22)
    - Troika Meeting 1974 (Box 186, Folder 23)
    - National, Regional General 1964-72 (Box 186, Folder 24)
    - Regional Office, Work Plans 1977-78 (Box 186, Folder 25)
  - Mid-Atlantic Region
    - Pennsylvania
      - Affiliation & Financial Data
        - 1976-77 (Box 186, Folder 26-27)
        - 1975 (Box 186, Folder 28)
        - 1974 (Box 186)
        - 1972-74 (Box 186, Folder 29-31)
      - Abortion
        - Data Sheet 1971 (Box 186, Folder 32)
        - General
          - 1973-74 (Box 186, Folder 33)
          - 1975-77 (Box 186)
      - Affiliate Resource Pool 1974 (Box 186, Folder 34)
      - Affiliation & Financial Data 1965-71 (Box 186, Folder 35-37)
      - Board Development Project
        - 1974 (Box 186, Folder 38)
        - 1976 (Box 186)
      - Committees
        - 1975-77 (Box 186, Folder 39-40)
        - 1970-74 (Box 186, Folder 41)
      - Medical Committee
        - 1977 (Box 186, Folder 42)
        - 1975-76 (Box 186, Folder 43)
        - 1973-74 (Box 186)
        - Minutes
          - 1974 (Box 186, Folder 44)
          - 1976 (Box 186)
      - Miscellaneous Committees, Minutes 1971-74 (Box 186, Folder 45)
      - Planning Committee Meeting, Minutes 1974 (Box 186, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence
        - 1976-77 (Box 186, Folder 47-48)
        - Derwent Suthers, Director 1975 (Box 186, Folder 49)
        - 1974 (Box 186, Folder 50)
        - Drewent Suthers, Director 1973 (Box 186, Folder 51)
        - Stanford-Burnheim, Director 1972-73 (Box 186, Folder 52)
        - Helen Stanford, Director 1964-72 (Box 186, Folder 53-60)
      - Philadelphia, Delegates, Members
        - 1966-74 (Box 186, Folder 61)
        - 1976-77 (Box 186)
      - Evaluation and Analysis of the Analytical Survey Questionnaire Study 1970-71 (Box 186, Folder 62)
      - Executive Directors, Council
        - Correspondence 1971 (Box 186, Folder 63)
        - Minutes 1971-73 (Box 186, Folder 64)
      - Federally Funded Family Planning Services 1972-73 (Box 186, Folder 65)
      - "The Frontiers of Family Planning: Where Do We Stand?" (To President & Executive Director) 1974 (Box 186, Folder 66)
  - Northeast Region, New York, Health System Agencies from 1976 (Box 186, Folder 67)
  - Mid-Atlantic Region
    - Pennsylvania
      - Philip J. Hedstrom, Resources Consultant 1973-74 (Box 186, Folder 68)
      - Implications to PP Affiliates of Remaining Unincorporated 1972 (Box 186, Folder 69)
      - Kay Knipe, Assistant Director of Resources 1972 (Box 186, Folder 70)
      - Leases 1972-74 (Box 186, Folder 71)
      - Memos, Mimeos 1973-74 (Box 186, Folder 72)
      - News Release 1972 (Box 186, Folder 73)
      - Memos, Mimeos
        - 1974 (Box 186, Folder 74)
        - 1976-77 (Box 186)
      - Papers, Helen P. Stanford 1968 (Box 186, Folder 75)
      - Personnel: Employment, Vacations, Leaves, Overtime, Terminations, etc.
        - 1972-74 (Box 186, Folder 76)
        - 1975-77 (Box 186)
      - Public Affairs
        - 1973-74 (Box 186, Folder 77)
        - 1975 (Box 186)
      - Procedural Statement on Regional & State-Wide Appointments 1973 (Box 186, Folder 78)
      - Projects 1968 (Box 186, Folder 79)
      - Philadelphia, Publicity
        - 1966-74 (Box 186, Folder 80)
        - 1975-77 (Box 186)
      - Questionnaire: Medical Services in Federally Funded Programs 1973 (Box 186, Folder 81)
      - Registry of Charitable Organizations in the State of Pennsylvania 1973 (Box 186, Folder 82)
      - Regional Chairman and/or Rep., correspondence
        - 1970-74 (Box 186, Folder 83)
        - 1975-77 (Box 186)
      - Regional Chairman's Report 1973 (Box 186, Folder 84)
      - Regional Representative's Report of PPFA
        - Annual Meeting, Atlanta 1977 (Box 186, Folder 85)
        - Annual Meeting 1973 (Box 186, Folder 86)
        - National Board & Executive Committee Meetings
          - 1974 (Box 186, Folder 87)
          - 1975-77 (Box 186)
        - Executive Committee Board & Regional Meetings 1969-73 (Box 186, Folder 88-92)
      - Reports, General
        - 1970-74 (Box 186, Folder 93)
        - 1975-77 (Box 186)
        - 1967-69 (Box 186, Folder 94-95)
      - Philadelphia, Reports, Helen Stanford 1965-66 (Box 187, Folder 1)
      - Resource Pool, Temporary Folder 1973 (Box 187, Folder 2)
      - Report on the Legal Aspects of Adoption, Sterilization & Abortion in Mid-Atlantic Region 1971 (Box 187, Folder 3)
      - A Review of the Mid-Atlantic Region, Helen P. Stanford 1972 (Box 187, Folder 4)
      - Task Force on Special Concerns 1975 (Box 187, Folder 5)
      - Technical Assistance
        - 1968-74 (Box 187, Folder 6)
        - 1975 (Box 187)
      - Workshop, Spring Conference
        - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania 1976 (Box 187, Folder 7)
        - Newark, New Jersey
          - Jan.-Sept.,1974 (Box 187, Folder 8)
          - Jan.-May, 1975 (Box 187)
        - Airlie House, Virginia 1974 (Box 187, Folder 9)
        - Spring Meeting, York, Pennsylvania 1973 (Box 187, Folder 10)
        - 8th Annual Spring Workshop, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania 1972 (Box 187, Folder 11)
      - Workshops
        - 1969 (Box 187, Folder 12)
        - 1971-74 (Box 187, Folder 13)
        - 1975-77 (Box 187)
        - 1966-70 (Box 187, Folder 14-16)
        - Uniform Accounting, Philadelphia 1967-68 (Box 187, Folder 17)
  - Great Lakes Region
    - Michigan
      - Abortion, General Correspondence
        - 1971-74 (Box 187, Folder 18)
        - 1975-79 (Box 187)
      - Abortion & Pregnancy Counseling Project
        - 1972-73 (Box 187, Folder 19)
        - 1979 (Box 187)
      - Affiliate Profiles
        - 1973-74 (Box 187, Folder 20)
        - 1975 (Box 187)
      - Affiliates Resource Pool 1974 (Box 187, Folder 21)
      - Affiliation & Financial Data
        - 1975-78 (Box 187, Folder 22-23)
        - 1971-74 (Box 187, Folder 24-25)
    - Indianapolis
      - Affiliation & Financial Data 1970 (Box 187, Folder 26)
      - Affiliation & Financial Data, Carl E. Speckman, Director 1964-69 (Box 187, Folder 27)
    - Michigan
      - Certification Area/Turf Area of Affiliation in the Great Lakes Region 1974 (Box 187, Folder 28)
      - 1970 CL-7 Annual Report Summary 1969-71 (Box 187, Folder 29)
      - Committees
        - 1975-78 (Box 187, Folder 30-31)
        - 1972-74 (Box 187, Folder 32)
        - Medical Committee
          - 1973-74 (Box 187, Folder 33)
          - 1976 (Box 187)
        - Long Range Planning Committee, Minutes 1974 (Box 187, Folder 34)
        - Medical Committee,Minutes
          - 1975 (Box 187, Folder 35)
          - 1973-74 (Box 187, Folder 36)
          - 1975-76 (Box 187, Folder 37-38)
      - Conference on the "Roles Women Play in Family Planning," Michigan 1974 (Box 187, Folder 39)
      - Consultant 1978 (Box 187, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence
        - Terry M. Granger, Great Lakes Regional Director 1980 (Box 187, Folder 41)
        - 1975-79 (Box 187, Folder 42-44)
        - Terrence Tiffany, Director 1974-71 (Box 187, Folder 45-48)
    - Indianapolis
      - Correspondence
        - Director 1970 (Box 187, Folder 49)
        - Carl E. Speckman, Director 1964-69 (Box 187, Folder 50-53)
    - Texas, Legal (Paul, Eve), Jesse Thomas, Asstant Regional Director 1978 (Box 187, Folder 54)
    - Michigan
      - Criteria for Categorizing Affiliates into Small, Medium & Large 1972 (Box 187, Folder 55)
      - Doris Critz, Resources Consultant 1975 (Box 187, Folder 56)
      - Executive Committee Meeting, Financial/Leadership Plight of Federation 1974 (Box 187, Folder 57)
      - Executive Directors Council 1971-74 (Box 187, Folder 58)
      - Eastern Regional Family Planning Conference, Family Planning, Funding Resources List 1972 (Box 187, Folder 59)
      - Fund Raising Orientation, Sessions 1974 (Box 187, Folder 60)
      - Indianapolis, Fund Raising Seminar 1974 (Box 187, Folder 61)
      - Group Purchase Plan: Gentec
        - 1974 (Box 187, Folder 62)
        - 1975 (Box 187)
    - Indiana
      - Leases, Correspondence
        - 1970-74 (Box 187, Folder 63)
        - 1976 (Box 187)
    - Michigan
      - Job Openings & Applicants 1972 (Box 187, Folder 64)
      - Material, Activity in State of Michigan 1978 (Box 187, Folder 65)
      - Medical Review Form 1973 (Box 187, Folder 66)
      - Memos, Mimeos, General
        - 1971-74 (Box 187, Folder 67)
        - 1975-77 (Box 187)
      - Methods of Circulating Patient Costs Per Visit (A Study) 1973 (Box 187, Folder 68)
      - Minimum Dues Formula w/ Revisions Proposed by Regional Council Executive Committee 1971 (Box 187, Folder 69)
      - Need/Resources Analysis, HEW Study 1972 (Box 187, Folder 70)
      - Organizational Chart 1973 (Box 187, Folder 71)
      - Orientation for New Executive Directors 1972-73 (Box 187, Folder 72)
      - Orientation for New Executive Directors (Box 187, Folder 73)
        - 1971 (Box 187)
        - 1975 (Box 187)
      - "The Great Lakes Region - An Overview," 1973 (Box 187, Folder 74)
      - Outline for Mini Regional Plan 1971 (Box 187, Folder 75)
      - Personnel: Employment, Vacations, Leaves, Overtime, Terminations, Etc.
        - 1972-74 (Box 187, Folder 76)
        - 1975-78 (Box 187)
      - Planned Parenthood as Service Provider, Past, Present and Future 1972 (Box 187, Folder 77)
      - Proposed Plan for the Seventies 1971-73 (Box 187, Folder 78)
    - Indianapolis
      - Projects 1969 (Box 187, Folder 79)
    - Michigan
      - Public Affairs
        - 1974 (Box 187, Folder 80)
        - 1975-76 (Box 187)
        - 1973 (Box 187, Folder 81)
    - Indianapolis
      - Publicity
        - 1967-1973 (Box 187, Folder 82)
        - 1977 (Box 187)
    - Michigan
      - Questionnaires 1973 (Box 187, Folder 83)
      - Procedures, Recertification, Team Review & Great Lakes Region Plan, Approved 1976 (Box 187, Folder 84)
      - Ronald Redfern, Resources Consultant 1973 (Box 187, Folder 85)
      - Regional Interagency Coordinating Council 1971-73 (Box 187, Folder 86)
    - Indiana
      - Regional Chairman and/or Representative, Correspondence
        - 1970-74 (Box 187, Folder 87)
        - 1975-78 (Box 187)
    - Michigan
      - Detroit, Regional Chairman's Reports
        - 1970-74 (Box 187, Folder 88)
        - 1977 (Box 187)
      - Regional Representatives Report of PPWP Executive Committee & Regional Representatives Meetings
        - 1970-74 (Box 187, Folder 89)
        - 1977 (Box 187)
      - Report by States of Developments Affecting Family Planning in the Region 1971 (Box 187, Folder 90)
      - Report to the Affiliation Committee 1972 (Box 187, Folder 91)
      - Reports, General
        - 1977, 1980 (Box 187, Folder 92)
        - 1966-74 (Box 187, Folder 93-96)
    - Indianapolis
      - Reports
        - General 1964-65 (Box 188, Folder 1)
        - Members
          - 1964-74 (Box 188, Folder 2)
          - 1975-77 (Box 188)
    - Michigan
      - Resources Development Seminar, Indianapolis, Indiana 1974 (Box 188, Folder 3)
      - Resolutions from the Great Lakes Plan 1980 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Great Lakes Region
    - Indianapolis
      - Review of Affiliate Federal Projects (OEO-HEW) 1969 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Michigan
      - Salaries: Affiliate Executive Directors, Selected Positions 1973 (Box 188, Folder 6)
      - State of the Region Reports 1976-77 (Box 188, Folder 7)
      - State Welfare Reimbursement Practices 1971 (Box 188, Folder 8)
      - State-Wide Affiliates 1972 (Box 188, Folder 9)
      - Sub-Regional Family Planning Conferences, Fall, 1971 (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - Indianapolis
      - Technical Assistance
        - 1968-74 (Box 188, Folder 11)
        - 1976-78 (Box 188)
    - Michigan
      - Technical Assistance Proposal, Affiliate Fund Raising 1972 (Box 188, Folder 12)
      - Technical Resources Pool 1974 (Box 188, Folder 13)
      - Regional Family Planning Conference, Columbus, Ohio 1971 (Box 188, Folder 14)
      - Volunteer Attitude Study 1972 (Box 188, Folder 15)
      - Wayne State University, Work Study Program 1971 (Box 188, Folder 16)
      - Annual Meeting, Dayton, Ohio 1977-78 (Box 188, Folder 17)
      - Spring Conference
        - Detroit, Michigan 1977 (Box 188, Folder 18)
        - Cleveland, Ohio 1976 (Box 188, Folder 19)
      - Annual Meeting, Chicago, Illinois
        - 1974 (Box 188, Folder 20)
        - 1975 (Box 188)
      - Spring Conference
        - Louisville, Kentucky 1974 (Box 188, Folder 21)
        - Notre Dame, South Bend, Indiana 1973 (Box 188, Folder 22)
      - PPWP, Proceeding College Workshop, Indiana University 1973 (Box 188, Folder 23)
      - Proceedings, I & E Workshop, Great Lakes Regional Council, Battle Creek 1972 (Box 188, Folder 24)
      - Workshops
        - Milwaukee, Wisconsin 1972 (Box 188, Folder 25)
        - Purdue University, Indiana 1970-71 (Box 188, Folder 26)
    - Indianapolis
      - Workshops, East Lansing, Michigan 1969-70 (Box 188, Folder 27)
    - Michigan
      - Workshop on Medical Standards 1977-78 (Box 188, Folder 28)
    - Indianapolis
      - Workshops
        - 1965-74 (Box 188, Folder 29)
        - 1975-78 (Box 188)
  - Midwest Region
    - Chicago, Illinois 1964 (Box 188, Folder 30)
    - Missouri
      - Abortion, General, Correspondence
        - 1970-74 (Box 188, Folder 31)
        - 1975-76 (Box 188)
      - Affiliation & Financial Data
        - 1975-77 (Box 188, Folder 32-34)
        - 1971-74 (Box 188, Folder 35-37)
        - Ralph D. Price, Director 1966-70 (Box 188, Folder 38-39)
      - Certification Area/Turf Area for Affiliates in the Midwest Region 1974 (Box 188, Folder 40)
      - College Program 1970-71 (Box 188, Folder 41)
      - Committees
        - 1975-76 (Box 188, Folder 42)
        - 1970-74 (Box 188, Folder 43)
        - Medical
          - 1977-78 (Box 188, Folder 44)
          - 1973-74 (Box 188, Folder 45)
          - 1975-76 (Box 188)
          - Minutes 1973 (Box 188, Folder 46)
      - Regional Resources Review, Committee, Minutes 1977 (Box 188, Folder 47)
      - Consultation Services to Federally Funded Programs, John Swall 1971-73 (Box 188, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence
        - 1975-77 (Box 188, Folder 49-51)
        - Director 1974 (Box 188, Folder 52)
        - Ralph D.L. Price, Director 1966-73 (Box 188, Folder 53-60)
      - Executive Directors
        - Meeting 1972 (Box 188, Folder 61)
        - Training 1972 (Box 188, Folder 62)
      - Family Planning Programs & Need for Expansion, States in the Midwest Region 1971 (Box 188, Folder 63)
      - IRS Examinations, Affiliate Audits 1977 (Box 188, Folder 64)
      - The Kansas City Times Series on Women and Medicine 1973 (Box 188, Folder 65)
      - Laws Passed in States in Midwest Region 1971 (Box 188, Folder 66)
      - Lease
        - 1973-74 (Box 188, Folder 67)
        - 1977 (Box 188)
      - Male Birth Control Pamphlet 1971 (Box 188, Folder 68)
      - Midwest Regional Assembly, Annual Spring Meeting, Minutes 1975 (Box 188, Folder 69)
      - Organizational Chart 1973 (Box 188, Folder 70)
      - Personnel: Employment, Vacations, Leaves, Overtime, Terminations, etc.
        - 1972-74 (Box 188, Folder 71)
        - 1975-77 (Box 188)
      - Private Fund Raising & Fees 1972 (Box 188, Folder 72)
      - Midwest Regional Assembly, Procedures
        - 1971-72 (Box 188, Folder 73)
        - 1976 (Box 188)
      - Projects 1969-71 (Box 188, Folder 74)
      - Public Affairs
        - 1973-74 (Box 188, Folder 75)
        - 1976-77 (Box 188)
      - Publicity, Ralph D.L. Price
        - 1966-74 (Box 188, Folder 76)
        - 1975-77 (Box 188)
      - Annual Reports 1971-72 (Box 188, Folder 77)
      - Report to the Affiliation Committee 1972 (Box 188, Folder 78)
      - Reports, General
        - 1973-74 (Box 188, Folder 79)
        - 1975-77 (Box 188)
      - Ralph D.L. Price, Director, Reports, General 1969-72 (Box 188, Folder 80-83)
      - Family Planning Training Workshops for Health & Welfare, Personnel 1966-72 (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Conferences
        - Midwest Region Regional Conference, St. Louis, Missouri 1976-77 (Box 189, Folder 2)
        - Des Moines, Iowa 1976 (Box 189, Folder 3)
        - Midwest Region Conference, Omaha, Nebraska 1974-75 (Box 189, Folder 4)
        - Xth Annual Conference, Missoula, Montana 1974 (Box 189, Folder 5)
        - Ninth Annual Conference, Sioux City 1973 (Box 189, Folder 6)
        - 8th Annual Midwest Regional Conference, Denver, Colorado 1972 (Box 189, Folder 7)
      - Workshops
        - St. Paul, Minnesota 1971 (Box 189, Folder 8)
        - Kansas City, Missouri 1970 (Box 189, Folder 9)
        - Des Moines, Iowa 1968-69 (Box 189, Folder 10)
        - General
          - 1970-74 (Box 189, Folder 11)
          - 1975-76 (Box 189)
        - Regional 1966-69 (Box 189, Folder 12)
      - Regional Representative's Report
        - PPWP Annual Meeting, San Antonio, Texas 1972 (Box 189, Folder 13)
        - National Board & Executive Committee Meetings
          - 1972-74 (Box 189, Folder 14)
          - 1975-77 (Box 189)
        - PPWP Executive Committee & Regional Representatives Meetings 1970-71 (Box 189, Folder 15-16)
      - Report of Board Meeting/Southeast Regional Meeting, 5/6-8/70; National Board Meeting, 1970 (Box 189, Folder 17)
      - Regional Representative's Report of the Executive Committee Meeting of PPWP 1969 (Box 189, Folder 18)
      - Services & Informational Material Provided to Affiliates in the Midwest 1973 (Box 189, Folder 19)
      - Student Placement in Community Organization, Marilyn Reinhardt 1972 (Box 189, Folder 20)
      - Technical Assistance 1968-71 (Box 189, Folder 21)
      - Service to Indians 1971-73 (Box 189, Folder 22)
      - Title IV: A Funding Source for Family Planning Programs, Ralph D.L. Price 1971-72 (Box 189, Folder 23)
      - Thomas Woods, Resources Consultant 1973-74 (Box 189, Folder 24)
      - Workshop, Interagency Family Planning Workshops 1970-71 (Box 189, Folder 25)
      - Ralph D.L. Price, Director, Reports
        - General 1966-69 (Box 189, Folder 26-27)
        - Members
          - 1965-74 (Box 189, Folder 28)
          - 1975-77 (Box 189)
      - Public Meeting Held to Discuss Need for Family Planning Services, Report 1971 (Box 189, Folder 29)
      - Midwest Regional Assembly 1971 (Box 189, Folder 30)
      - Regional Chairman and/or Representative, Correspondence
        - 1970-74 (Box 189, Folder 31)
        - 1975-77 (Box 189)
  - Southwest Region
    - Texas
      - Library
        - 1975-76 (Box 189, Folder 32)
        - 1974 (Box 189)